...and I made a teeny-tiny mistake
on the specifications for the diverter valve.
How teeny-tiny?
It's gonna fail after about 10 flushes.
- But the mission is for six months.
- That's the code red.
(Howard:)It's kind of like a jack-in-the-box.
No one knows exactly when...
(Howard:)...but at some point, something way worse
than a puppet is gonna pop out of that box.
(Sheldon:)Have you notified NASA?
You crazy? What am I gonna say?
I screwed up your toilet...
(Howard:)...and pretty soon there's gonna be crap
floating all over your nice space station?
(Leonard:)What are you gonna do?
(Howard:)I'm gonna figure out how to fix it,
then I'll tell them.
(Leonard:)So, what do you need us for?
(Raj:)He can't figure out how to fix it.
(Howard:)You said you were gonna be supportive.
(Raj:)I'm trying. But you have to admit,
this is pretty damn funny.
(Sheldon:)I agree.
It's a juxtaposition of the nature
of space exploration...
(Sheldon:)...against the banality of a malfunctioning
toilet that provides the comic fodder here.
[LAUGHS]
(Sheldon:)Check your messages.